Andrew Eisenberg collection of East African commercial sound recordings AD.MC.035
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Series II: Jamal Hafidh Jahadhmy collection, circa 1930-1975; 191 audio_recordings
  - Musa Maruf
    - Musa Maruf: Madina, 1 audio_recording 17.8 MB (Folder 415)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:21.
    - Musa Maruf: Mpenzi Wangu Kanitoka, 1952-1961; 1 audio_recording 15.8 MB (Folder 416)
      Serial number: Jambo, EA.421, J.R. 773. Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:58.
    - Musa Maruf: Zimekutanika, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.7 MB (Folder 417)
    - Musa Maruf: Bombay Safari, N/A; 1 audio_recording 112.0 MB (Folder 418)
      Original format: Magnetic tape. Other notes: According to Jamal Hafidh, this recording was a late-career release. Live, distributed on magnetic reel. Duration: 10:34.
    - Musa Maruf: Diamond Jubilee 1, N/A; 1 audio_recording 53.2 MB (Folder 419)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc {?]. Other notes: Later (live) version of the Jambo Records single. Duration: 5:01.
    - Musa Maruf: Diamond Jubilee 2, N/A; 1 audio_recording 38.8 MB (Folder 420)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc [?]. Other notes: Later (live) version of the Jambo Records single. Duration: 3:39.
      Jambo
    - Musa Maruf: Fungua Uso Wako, N/A; 1 audio_recording 51.1 MB (Folder 421)
      Original format: Magnetic tape [?]. Other notes: According to Jamal Hafidh, this was a late-career release. Duration: 4:49.
    - Musa Maruf: Kijiti-Toto la Bandia, N/A; 1 audio_recording 71.2 MB (Folder 422)
      Original format: Magnetic tape [?]. Other notes: According to Jamal Hafidh, this was a late-career release. Duration: 6:43.
    - Musa Maruf: Nani Kama Wewe, 1 audio_recording 74.0 MB (Folder 423)
      Original format: Magnetic tape [?]. Other notes: According to Jamal Hafidh, this was a late-career release. Duration: 6:59.
    - Musa Maruf: Rupiya-Layla na Matinuni, 1 audio_recording 79.3 MB (Folder 424)
      Original format: Magnetic tape [?]. Other notes: According to Jamal Hafidh, this was a late-career release. Duration: 7:29.
    - Musa Maruf: Unguja-Bendera, N/A; 1 audio_recording 141.5 MB (Folder 425)
      Original format: Magnetic tape [?]. Other notes: According to Jamal Hafidh, this was a late-career release. Duration: 13:21.
  - Mwana Amina
    - Mwana Amina: Thalatha Shahari 1, 1 audio_recording 15.4 MB (Folder 426)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:54.
    - Mwana Amina: Thalatha Shahari 2, 1 audio_recording 16.0 MB (Folder 427)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:01.
  - Ngoma ya Bangamawi
    - Ngoma ya Bangamawi: Kilele Manga, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.4 MB (Folder 428)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:43.
  - Ngoma ya Jamii Kheirat
    Serial number: Columbia, W63263, WEii. Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:53.
    - Ngoma ya Jamii Kheirat: Nipe Changu Kitumbua, circa 1930; 1 audio_recording 15.0 MB (Folder 429)
      Columbia, W63263, WE11. Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:49.
  - Ngomi ya Msondo
    - Ngoma ya Msondo: Akija Tumzuie Simba, circa 1930; 1 audio_recording 15.4 MB (Folder 430)
      Serial number: Columbia, WE.14. Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:54.
  - Ngomi ya Udi
    - Ngoma ya Udi: Mukina, 1 audio_recording 15.4 MB (Folder 431)
      Original format: Disk. Duration: 2:54.
  - Omar Awadh Albany
    - Omar Awadh Albany: Antal Hayatu, N/A; 1 audio_recording 32.4 MB (Folder 432)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc [?]. Duration: 3:03.
    - Omar Awadh Albany: Nahnu Shabab, 1 audio_recording 30.9 MB (Folder 433)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc [?]. Duration: 2:55.
    - Omar Awadh Albany: Nahoni Anka Adhali, 1 audio_recording 33.3 MB (Folder 434)
    - Omar Awadh Albany: Shakarta Dhamaa, N/A; 1 audio_recording 33.9 MB (Folder 435)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:12.
  - Omar bin Juma
    - Omar Bin Juma: Amma Baadu Nduyangu 1, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.9 MB (Folder 436)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:00.
    - Omar Bin Juma: Amma Baadu Nduyangu 2, N/A; 1 audio_recording 16.2 MB (Folder 437)
  - Ramadhan & Subeit bin Ambar
    - Ramadhan and Subeit bin Ambar: Taksim Nahwandi - wimbo wa vinanda viwili, circa 1930; 1 audio_recording 30.2 MB (Folder 438)
      Original format: Columbia, 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:51.
  - Ramadhan Faki
    - Ramadhan Faki: Dezi Kanambiya, 1 audio_recording 16.2 MB (Folder 439)
    - Ramadhan Faki: Ewe Roho Yangu, N/A; 1 audio_recording 13.1 MB (Folder 440)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:28.
    - Ramadhan Faki: Ila Kafa Ndugu Zangu, N/A; 1 audio_recording 13.4 MB (Folder 441)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:23.
    - Ramadhan Faki: Shombo Binti Hasani, N/A; 1 audio_recording 13.5 MB (Folder 442)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:33.
    - Ramadhan Faki: Wacheni Yenu Tamaa, N/A; 1 audio_recording 12.8 MB (Folder 443)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:25.
  - Rashid Mussa
    - Rashid Mussa: Jipeleleze Part 1, N/A; 1 audio_recording 16.2 MB (Folder 444)
      Serial number: A.S.P.Y.L. (Culture), URT 102. Original format: 45 rpm vinyl disc. Label: Afro-Shirazi Party Youth League (Zanzibar), Made in India by the Gramophone Company of India Limited. Duration: 3:03.
    - Rashid Mussa: Jipeleleze Part 2, N/A; 1 audio_recording 16.0 MB (Folder 445)
      Serial number: A.S.P.Y.L. (Culture), URT 102. Original format: 45 rpm vinyl disc. Label: Afro-Shirazi Party Youth League (Zanzibar), Made in India by the Gramophone Company of India Limited. Duration: 3:01.
  - Salim Abdulla / Cuban Marimba Band
    - Salim Abdulla/Cuban Marimba Band: Kacha Cha, circa 1965-1975; 1 audio_recording 14.6 MB (Folder 446)
      Serial number: Mzuri, AL 56, HL 7-28. Original format: 45 rpm vinyl disc. Duration: 2:45.
    - Salim Abdulla/Cuban Marimba Band: Ngoma Iko Huku, circa 1965-1975; 1 audio_recording 14.4 MB (Folder 447)
      Serial number: Mzuri, AL 55, HL 7-28. Original format: 45 rpm vinyl disc. Duration: 2:43.
  - Siti Binti Saad
    - Siti Binti Saad: Baashraf, N/A; 1 audio_recording 13.4 MB (Folder 448)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:31.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Beru Beru, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.0 MB (Folder 449)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Binaadamu, 1 audio_recording 16.3 MB (Folder 450)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:04.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Dua, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.7 MB (Folder 451)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Ee Baba Pakistan, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.5 MB (Folder 452)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Enyi Wakhiyari, N/A; 1 audio_recording 11.5 MB (Folder 453)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:10.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Fanya Utakalo, N/A; 1 audio_recording 20.2 MB (Folder 454)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Hasidi, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.8 MB (Folder 455)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:48.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Hero, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.4 MB (Folder 456)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Mbembeleze Mtoto, Part 1, circa 1930; 1 audio_recording (Folder 457)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Mbembeleze Mtoto, Part 2, circa 1930; 1 audio_recording 15.0 MB (Folder 458)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Ilahi Wadudi, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.3 MB (Folder 459)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:42.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Itabu 1, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.2 MB (Folder 460)
      Physical characteristics or original
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:51.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Itabu 2, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.5 MB (Folder 461)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Kaifa Yakuna 1, 1 audio_recording 12.6 MB (Folder 462)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Kaifa Yakuna 2, 1 audio_recording 11.6 MB (Folder 463)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:11.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Kitandawili Tega 1, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.5 MB (Folder 464)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:44.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Kuvaa Refoma, 1 audio_recording 14.6 MB (Folder 465)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Kuwa Mbali Mbali, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.0 MB (Folder 466)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Mahaba ya Dhati, N/A; 1 audio_recording 27.9 MB (Folder 467)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 5:16.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Mapengo, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.2 MB (Folder 468)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Mawaidha, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.4 MB (Folder 469)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Mayowe, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.6 MB (Folder 470)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Mazoweya, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.2 MB (Folder 471)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:40.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Mzoweya Punda 1, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.2 MB (Folder 472)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Mzoweya Punda 2, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.9 MB (Folder 473)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Nacheka Sina Furaha 1, 1 audio_recording 12.8 MB (Folder 474)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:24.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Nacheka Sina Furaha 2, 1 audio_recording 12.8 MB (Folder 475)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Nnayokwambiya, 1 audio_recording 15.5 MB (Folder 476)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Queeni, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.6 MB (Folder 477)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Taireni Waganga 1, 1930; 1 audio_recording 15.3 MB (Folder 478)
      Original format: Odeon, A 24 21 46, Br.0.285, 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:53.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Taireni Waganga 2, 1930; 1 audio_recording 15.2 MB (Folder 479)
      Original format: Odeon, A 24 21 46, Br.0.286, 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:52.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Toka Haya Nenda, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.2 MB (Folder 480)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Toka Haya Nenda 2, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.2 MB (Folder 481)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Utaniathiri, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.5 MB (Folder 482)
    - Siti Binti Saad: Yalaiti Part 1/Yalaiti Part 2, 1939; 1 audio_recording 24.6 MB (Folder 483)
      Serial number: Columbia, EO.4002. Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 4:38.
    - Siti Binti Saad: Ziwache Khasama, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.0 MB (Folder 484)
  - Siti Ganduri and Party
    - Siti Ganduri and Party of Ras Maalin Revue: Binaadamu Havumi, 1 audio_recording 16.2 MB (Folder 485)
    - Siti Ganduri and Party of Ras Maalin Revue: Chukuwa Maziwa, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.7 MB (Folder 486)
    - Siti Ganduri and Party of Ras Maalin Revue: Dunia, N/A; 1 audio_recording 17.2 MB (Folder 487)
    - Siti Ganduri and Party of Ras Maalin Revue: Kitabu Nimekifunga, N/A; 1 audio_recording 15.5 MB (Folder 488)
    - Siti Ganduri and Party of Ras Maalin Revue: Siwakati Huu, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.5 MB (Folder 489)
      Serial number: Columbia, EO.2131. Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:44.
    - Siti Ganduri and Party of Ras Maalin Revue: Una Mitulinga, 1 audio_recordings 13.4 MB (Folder 490)
      Serial number: Columbia, EO.2131. Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:31.
    - Siti Ganduri and Party of Ras Maalin Revue: Yomi Nimechoka, N/A; 1 audio_recording 16.8 MB (Folder 491)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:10.
  - Siti Kiburi
    - Siti Kiburi: Masikini Mwanangu, 1 audio_recording 17.4 MB (Folder 492)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:17.
    - Siti Kiburi: Mpenzi Wangu, N/A; 1 audio_recording 17.2 MB (Folder 493)
  - Siti Mayasa and Party
    - Siti Mayasa and Party: Ibinaa Imefurahi, 1950; 1 audio_recording 16.1 MB (Folder 494)
      Original format: Jambo, 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:02.
    - Siti Mayasa and Party: Nipa Penseli, 1950; 1 audio_recording 16.6 MB (Folder 495)
      Original format: Jambo, 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:08.
    - Siti Mayasa and Party: Raha ya Mauwa, 1950; 1 audio_recording 16.5 MB (Folder 496)
      Original format: Jambo, 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:06.
    - Siti Mayasa and Party: Wangu wa Anasa, 1950; 1 audio_recording 16.0 MB (Folder 497)
      Original format: Jambo, 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:01.
  - Siti wa Habu
    - Siti wa Habu: Jumla ya Maashiki, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.4 MB (Folder 498)
    - Siti wa Habu: Rahimu Inua Ngao, N/A; 1 audio_recording 18.7 MB (Folder 499)
      Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 3:31.
  - Subeit bin Ambar
    - Subeit Bin Ambar: Taqsim Hijazai, circa 1930; 1 audio_recording 29.9 MB (Folder 500)
      Serial number: Columbia, WE.25. Original format: 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 2:49.
    - Subeit Bin Ambar: Taqsim, 1 audio_recording 4.1 MB (Folder 501)
      Original format: Columbia, 78 rpm shellac disc. Duration: 0:46.
  - Three Brothers
    - Three Brothers: Masikini Nyota, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.6 MB (Folder 502)
    - Three Brothers: Nimeyaswadiki, N/A; 1 audio_recording 14.8 MB (Folder 503)
    - Three Brothers: Okay My Dali, N/A; 1 audio_recording 16.1 MB (Folder 504)
  - Young India Band
    - Bila Shaka Kweli Nakupenda, _ref853; 1 audio_recording 17.3 MB (Folder 505)
      Duration: 3:16.
    - Cheza Cheza Mwanangu, _ref854; 1 audio_recording 16.3 MB (Folder 506)
      Duration: 3:05.
    - Ee Mungu wa Mbinguni, N/A; _ref855; 1 audio_recording 17.1 MB (Folder 507)
      Duration: 3:13.
    - Fikisha Barua Na, _ref856; 1 audio_recording 16.7 MB (Folder 508)
      General
      Duplicate of recording that is also available in folder 296 of this collection.
      Duration: 3:09.
    - Hewala Hewala, N/A; _ref857; 1 audio_recording 16.8 MB (Folder 509)
      Duration: 3:10.
    - Hii Ni Mwisho, N/A; _ref858; 1 audio_recording 13.5 MB (Folder 510)
      Duration: 2:32.
    - Hizi Kipenzi, N/A; _ref859; 1 audio_recording 13.9 MB (Folder 511)
      Duration: 2:37.
    - Kila Niliza, N/A; _ref860; 1 audio_recording 13.8 MB (Folder 512)
      Duration: 2:36.
    - Kugombana Kupatana, _ref861; 1 audio_recording 16.4 MB (Folder 513)
      Duplicate of recording that is also available in folder 298 of this collection.
      Duration: 3:06.
    - Kwaheri Tunaagana, _ref862; 1 audio_recording 15.0 MB (Folder 514)
      Duration: 2:50.
    - Leo Ni Siku Ya Furaha, N/A; _ref863; 1 audio_recording 17.1 MB (Folder 515)
    - Macho Yako Kama Nyota, N/A; _ref864; 1 audio_recording 17.7 MB (Folder 516)
      Duration: 3:20.
    - Mahaba ya Siku Hizi, N/A; _ref865; 1 audio_recording 17.0 MB (Folder 517)
    - Mbio Mbio, N/A; _ref866; 1 audio_recording 17.2 MB (Folder 518)
      Duration: 3:15.
    - Moyo Wangu, N/A; _ref867; 1 audio_recording 17.8 MB (Folder 519)
      Duration: 3:22.
    - Naliota Ndoto, _ref869; 1 audio_recording 17.8 MB (Folder 520)
      Duration: 3:21
    - Nakukumbuka, _ref868; 1 audio_recording 17.0 MB (Folder 521)
      Duration: 3:12.
    - Nenda, Njoo, N/A; _ref870; 1 audio_recording 19.5 MB (Folder 522)
      Duration: 3:41.
    - Nenda Zako, Nimechoke, N/A; _ref871; 1 audio_recording 15.0 MB (Folder 523)
      Duplicate of recording that is also available in folder 302 of this collection.
    - Nimeona Sura Ya, _ref872; 1 audio_recording 16.9 MB (Folder 524)
      Duplicate of recording that is also available in folder 303 of this collection.
      Duration: 3:11.
    - Ninasikitika, _ref873; 1 audio_recording 16.5 MB (Folder 525)
      Duration: 3:07.
    - Njoo, N/A; _ref874; 1 audio_recording 16.0 MB (Folder 526)
      Duration: 3:01.
    - Njoo Kwangu, N/A; _ref875; 1 audio_recording 13.5 MB (Folder 527)
    - Picha Picha Yako, N/A; _ref876; 1 audio_recording 14.9 MB (Folder 528)
      Duplicate of recording that is also available in folder 304 of this collection.
      Duration: 2:49.
    - Sasa Tutacheza, N/A; _ref877; 1 audio_recording 16.5 MB (Folder 529)
    - Sauti Yako Nzuri, N/A; _ref878; 1 audio_recording 16.1 MB (Folder 530)
      Duration: 3:02.
    - Sema Sasa, N/A; _ref879; 1 audio_recording 15.7 MB (Folder 531)
      Duplicate of recording that is also available in folder 305 of this collection.
      Duration: 2:57.
    - Upepo Baridi, N/A; _ref880; 1 audio_recording 16.9 MB (Folder 532)
- TESTING: Series III: Audiocassettes, N/A; 0 audio_recordings
  Series 3: Digital audio transferred from commercially produced audiocassette recordings acquired by Eisenberg in Mombasa between 2004 and 2006. [yet to be processed]
  - Angelike Twist 1960's: John Nzene (Option 1, adding all tracks to PhysTech notes per side), AD_MC_035_ref0004; 1 Cassettes
    - Side A, AD_MC_035_ref0004_SideA; 1 audio_recordings What do we put here? Do we enter how many tracks for this side? Is the number 1 correct if this is multiple tracks?
      How should write this:
      1. John Nzene: Angelike Twist: Track 1. File Size: 96 MB. Duration: 2:47
      Or
      2. John Nzene: Veronika Mpenzi: Track 3. (104.9 MB) (3:02)
      John Nzene: Kuowa Ni Kuzuri: Track 4 102 MB 2:57 John Nzene: Urafiki Nikishaowa: Track 5 98 MB 2:50 John Nzene: Elizabeth Wangu: Track 6 109.7 MB 3:10 John Nzene: Makarani: Track 7 99.1 MB 2:52 John Nzene: Newachopo Kajulu: Track 8 102.7 MB 2:58
    - Side B, AD_MC_035_ref0004_SideB; 1 audio_recording What do we put here? Do we enter how many tracks for this side? Is the number 1 correct if this is multiple tracks?
      How should we write this:
      1. John Nzene: Amina Twist: Track 1. File Size: 101.3 MB. Running Time: 2:56
      2. John Nzene: Esther Acha Maringo: Track 2 (114.1 MB) (3:18)
      John Nzene: Twist Ni Nzuri: Track 3 92.2 MB 2:40 John Nzene: Jirani Wabaya: Track 4 113.1 MB 3:16 John Nzene: Ndugu Zangu: Track 5 105.1 MB 3:02 John Nzene: Heshima Ya Zamani: Track 6 100.4 MB 2:54 John Nzene: Sikitiko: Track 7 104.9 MB 3:02 John Nzene: Herina Atieno: Track 8 95.3 MB 2:46
  - Bango: Teusi Five (Option 2, adding all tracks to General note per side), AD_MC_035_ref0007; 1 Cassettes
    - Side A, AD_MC_035_ref0007_SideA; 1 audio_recordings Same questions as previous example
      See notes from Option 1 as to how to list these.
      Teusi Five: Bango: Track 1 187.9 MB 5:26 Teusi Five: Malikia: Track 2 153.2 MB 4:26 Teusi Five: Jambo Bwana: Track 3 184.6 MB 5:21 Teusi Five: Moyo Tulia: Track 4 160.1 MB 4:38 Teusi Five: Ni Hone Raha: Track 5 165.1 MB 4:47
    - Side B, AD_MC_035_ref007_SideB; 1 audio_recordings Same questions as previous
      Teusi Five: Shauri Moyo: Track 1 168.6 MB 4:53 Teusi Five: Utajua Mwenyewe: Track 2 176.5 MB 5:06 Teusi Five: Debe Tupu: Track 3 158.3 MB 4:35 Teusi Five: Simba: Track 4 163.1 MB 4:43 Teusi Five: Twende Tu: Track 5 168.6 MB 4:53
  - RP DELETE: Best of Abbasi Mzee: Egyptian Musical Club (Option 3, listing all tracks in each side individually), AD_MC_035_ref0009; 1 Cassettes
    - Side A
      - Egyptian Musical Club: Yatima: Track 1, AD_MC_ref0009_SideA_001; 1 audio_recording File Size: 455.9MB
        Running Time: 13:11
        Composer: Abbassi Mzee Label: F.K Mitha & Sons, Kings Brothers, Wananchi Stores
      - Egyptian Musical Club: Akufanyiaye Ubaya: Track 2, AD_MC_ref0009_SideA_0002; 1 audio_recording File Size: 584.7MB
        Running Time: 16:55
        Composer: Abbassi Mzee
        Label: F.K Mitha & Sons, Kings Brothers, Wananchi Stores
    - Side B
      - Egyptian Musical Club: Alianza Peke Peke: Track 1, AD_MC_035_ref0009_SideB_001; 1 audio_recording File Size: 360.7MB
        Running Time: 10.26
      - Egyptian Musical Club: Fitina Mbaya: Track 2, 1 audio_recording File Size: 682.8MB
        Running Time: 19.45
- Series III: Audiocassettes
  - Riyadhalamu Maulidi Yalamu: [Unknown], 2005; AD_MC_035_ref1001; 1 Cassettes
  - A, Skh. Abdililahi Nassir/ Mwambao: Skh. Abidillahi Nassir/Mwambao, AD_MC_035_ref1001.5; 1 Cassettes
  - 20 Best of E.A's 1950s: The African Sounds, AD_MC_035_ref1002; 1 Cassettes
  - Ali Mkali 1: Ali Mkali, AD_MC_035_ref1003; 1 Cassettes
  - Angelike Twist 1960's: John Nzene, AD_MC_035_ref1004; 1 Cassettes
  - Ay: Raha Kamili, AD_MC_035_ref1005; 1 Cassettes
  - Bamba Shi-Shishi 2: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1006; 1 Cassettes
  - Bango: Teusi Five, AD_MC_035_ref1007; 1 Cassettes
  - Bei Kali: JOSE Chameleon, AD_MC_035_ref1008; 1 Cassettes
  - Best of Abbasi Mzee: Egyptian Musical Club, AD_MC_035_ref1009; 1 Cassettes
  - Best Song of Bongo Flavor Volume no. 17: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1010; 1 Cassettes
  - Best of Rush A Roho: Mwanahawa Ally, AD_MC_035_ref1011; 1 Cassettes
  - Best Song Of Bongo Flavor Vol - 16: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1012; 1 Cassettes
  - New Bhalo No. 3: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1013; 1 Cassettes
  - Bi Kidude: Fatma Mbaraka, AD_MC_035_ref1014; 1 Cassettes
  - Bwana-Adi No. 2: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1015; 1 Cassettes
  - Cinderella: Mighty King Kong, AD_MC_035_ref1016; 1 Cassettes
  - Culture: Makame Faki, AD_MC_035_ref1017; 1 Cassettes
  - Culture Vol.2: Mwanaacha Hassan, AD_MC_035_ref1018; 1 Cassettes
  - Diamond Modern Taarab: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1019; 1 Cassettes
  - Diamond Star: Sitara & Party, AD_MC_35_ref1021; 1 Cassettes
  - Diamond Stars. Nyota Za Almasi. Hamtaki Tule: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1022; 1 Cassettes
  - East African Melody 2001: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1023; 1 Cassettes
  - Girlfriend: The Sound Track: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1024; 1 Cassettes
  - Golden Star No. 6: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1025; 1 Cassettes
  - Habib & Abdalla 1: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1026; 1 Cassettes
  - Habib & Abdalla 2: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1027; 1 Cassettes
  - Hakuna Matata: Teddy Kalanda Harrison, AD_MC_035_ref1028; 1 Cassettes
  - Hassan Mix: Hassan, AD_MC_035_ref1029; 1 Cassettes
  - Ikasie Saa Msondo: Omar Mzamil, 1974; AD_MC_035_ref1030; 1 Cassettes
  - Itenzi Wa Mwana Kupona: Kaswida Ya Hussein Badawy, AD_MC_035_ref1031; 1 Cassettes
  - Jawima Orch Nukaa Super International: Jacob William Maunda, AD_MC_035_ref1032; 1 Cassettes
  - Jaydee Moto: Jaydee Moto, 2004; AD_MC_035_ref1033; 1 Cassettes
  - JKT No. 1: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1034; 1 Cassettes
  - Johar Orchestra 1B: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1035; 1 Cassettes
  - Johari No. 1: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1036; 1 Cassettes
  - Juma Balo 079: Juma Balo, AD_MC_035_ref1037; 1 Cassettes
  - Kadara 1: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1038; 1 Cassettes
  - Kali Za Taarab: 155A Matona, AD_MC_035_ref1039; 1 Cassettes
  - Kali Za Taarab Remixes: Patricia Hillary and Elizabeth Sijila, AD_MC_035_ref1040; 1 Cassettes
  - Kathukuni 2000 Vol. Two: Kamwana Kiteme, AD_MC_035_ref1041; 1 Cassettes
  - Kidampa Nuksi Volume 8: Sitara Bute & Diamond Star Musical Club, AD_MC_035_ref1042; 1 Cassettes
  - Kidumbaki Asilia Vol. 3: Makame Faki, AD_MC_035_ref1043; 1 Cassettes
  - Kiroboto: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1044; 1 Cassettes
  - Lady's Choice: Mighty King Kong, AD_MC_035_ref1045; 1 Cassettes
  - Leo Band: Leo, AD_MC_035_ref1046; 1 Cassettes
  - Live Show at Ngome Kongwe 2001: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1047; 1 Cassettes
  - Machozi Ya Huba: Bi Kidude Zanzibar, AD_MC_035_ref1048; 1 Cassettes
  - Makhuluku Taabu: Dumbak Music Masters, AD_MC_035_ref1049; 1 Cassettes
  - Malaika: Fadhili William, 1960; AD_MC_035_ref1050; 1 Cassettes
  - Malika 8: Malika, AD_MC_035_ref1051; 1 Cassettes
  - Mapepe: Kingwendu, AD_MC_035_ref1052; 1 Cassettes
  - Mapinduzi Halisi: Proffessor Jay, AD_MC_035_ref1053; 1 Cassettes
  - Markaz Swalihina - Samai: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1054; 1 Cassettes
  - Matano 1: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1055; 1 Cassettes
  - Matano 2: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1056; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulid Machaprala with Nadi Ikhwani Safaa Zanzibar Vol. 3: Maulid Machaprala & Nadi Ikhwani Safaa Zanzibar, AD_MC_035_ref1057; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi & Sitara 1: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1058; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 9: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1060; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 10: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1061; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 15: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1062; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 19: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1063; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 20: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1064; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 20: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1065; 1 Cassettes